Hello Hello friend, welcome to our
YouTube channel Technical friends, I am
bringing you job information rule out
friends, this repeat from ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance, from unwanted bank,
footprint on anniversary sitting behind, if you all
go from any estate of Bharti India, then here you
can apply online, 102 number
vacancies for which you can apply from all over India,
his wife's name is
Unit Manager, earlier also vacancies were released on his channel
but the vacancies were less but on this one, it was
pan India recruitment
hunter, total number of vacancies, you can
apply from all over India, what are the
eligibility criteria,
who are the people who can do this, how long will the
salary be, we will talk about all the things
in detail, so
watch the video carefully from the beginning till the end or
watch it completely so that you get to know every single thing, all the
details, then you will decide yourself
whether you want to apply for it or
not and any  Any time you feel that
you don't have to apply for this,
you have got complete information,
you will find the link in the description,
those who want to apply for any other rep,
you will get more videos on the i button above,
you
can apply for those rep minutes, if you are
not interested in this tweet, then their
responsibilities are from this, from a quarter inch,
unit manager, recruitment agency sales,
again its request is that from one to
two years of experience has been asked, that is,
if you have experience then you
can apply, if you do
not have experience then you can apply now,
from 102 number vacancy, pan India recruitment, that is,
location, you are going to
live across India, you will start applying,
friends, there you will see the option to
select your location, whatever your
question is today or the place where you
want to work, you can select that question here,
but keep one thing
in mind that if you  Apply only if you know the local language of that place.
This
point can lead to your application being
rejected. So keep this thing
in mind. Apart from that, friends, if we talk about
responsibilities, then you have to form a team of
advisors who
work for Duki Insurance and they know how to
motivate them so that they can
complete the target. You
get a sales target, which you have to
contact everyone and then whatever
your minister target or whatever it is for, you have to do it.
You
send the target. Now it is a button job, the
salary is good in this and your
career is also quite good.
If you are interested in doing a work, then you
can do it. If you are selected, then
if you do not like the work further, then
you can leave that work. Here no one will make
you fill much papers etc.
So keep this thing also in mind that when you
apply, after selection,
your selection can be done through online assessment test
or interview.
The examination is going to be held here and
you have to click without any fees, so do it
because when you go to the website of its Prabhu Unit Manager,
you will
definitely find it somewhere or the other. This simply
means that many people must be joining
this and many people must be leaving it.
If you
want to see the experience, if you
can work then you can apply. The job will be
difficult, you will definitely get a good salary,
but it depends on you
how much work you can do. So this is a repeat,
friends, you can apply for Hunter Vacancy.
I have told you the role.
Talking about qualification,
whatever your qualification is, if you have done graduation then
you
can definitely take it, but if something worse than Edison is there then
you can apply for PIMP.
You can apply with experience.
If you do not have experience then
you can apply now, but
you should have knowledge of banking products, banking, which is a financial service,
in the assessment test.  You will also be
asked the same things related to banking and related to it and if you have knowledge of all these things then
only you will be able to do this work, so
read this thing so that if you are selected and
you are called for the interview of online assessment test, then you will be able to do it a little bit, so
friends, this information is
given on their official website, I will
not tell you about the salary here, but if you are
selected then your incentives can be more than the salary,
if you keep doing
this for a year, then
friends, the salary here you
can get is more than 2500, it depends on where
you come from, if you are
in metro cities and apply for there and you get
selected there, then
you can get a salary up to 30 thousand at the same destination,
but if you
come from this model town, then your salary there
can be 120, phase and work
incentives are separate, so this
Friends, the information given on the final official website, if
you feel that you should wait for this, then
in the link description it is given that
delete all these things, you will come to know about many things,
rest of the friends, take all these
things, okay, okay,
selection process, now let's come to the main thing,
how to apply, many people face the
problem that the application is there but it is not
happening, so to apply, first of all
you have to click on take, now
here friends, two things are very
important, the first thing which is
important is that the
size of your resume should be 3MB, it should be
in two MP3 folders, it should be
in PDF format, the document format
menu should be there and here the information about the format is
given that if even one of these two things is
wrong, then it will come here,
but despite both these things being correct,
many times it gets selected here, there can be
many reasons behind it,
otherwise if this has happened to you, then you should
try only Morpheme, this try will work for
you  The applications will definitely be submitted,
apart from that, here you have to select whatever you want to apply for, for the City SP City,
after relaxing, you have to
click on the check here and submit the application here,
as if you have submitted,
your application is submitted, after that you do
not have to do anything, whatever will be the effective recruitment
process, you will be
informed through email, but let me tell you one thing again
that there is no application fee at all,
if you have any such check and you get a
call from a number, you get an SMS, an
email in which money is demanded from you, then it is
from a fake,
you should not read into their cycles, if you want to apply then do it through
this method, so the method
I have told you, at least half of your
application, your resume, your
data will remain absolutely secure, so this is the
method of applying friends, hence
in Pawn Inch Life Insurance, I hope
that you have understood how to apply
and for which recruitment you can apply, the
unit manager's desk is absolutely  You
can apply easily, see this, I will be
able to watch this video and will meet
you again, till then take
care of yourself.